BRAC Additional Records 5735
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Abandonment - Bush Terminal Railroad, Entire Line in Kings County, New York and Hudson County, New Jersey, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Abandonments - Central Railroad of New Jersey (General), 1972 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  April-October 1972
- Grievances - Fort Worth and Denver Railway; Abandonments, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  January-November 1971
- Abandonments - Illinois Central, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- abandonments - Beaver, Meade, and Englewood Railroad Company, 1973-1975 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  November 8, 1973-May 1975
- Abandonments - Southern Pacific Transportation Company, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  October 4, 1973
- Abandonment - Petition to take up and discontinue use of tracks at Havana, Illinois - Chicago and Illinois Midland Railway Company, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous Files, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 16)
- Research Department (General), 1968-1978 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  Duplicate File. 1968-December 1978
- Research and Education, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  January-October 1979
- Research and Education, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 19)
- Library News, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 20)
- International President's Bulletin, 1965-1976 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  January 1, 1965-June 1976
- Hospital Association, 1966-1979 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  January 1, 1966-December 1979
- Atlantic Coast Line Hospital Association, 1960-1961 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  1960-July 1961
- Hospital Associations - Northern Pacific Terminal Company of Oregon, 1960-1965 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  1960-July 1965
- Hospital Association - Milwaukee Hospital Association, 1964-1975 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  1964-January 1975
- Hospital Associations - Burlington Northern, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Hospital Associations - Denver and Rio Grande Western, 1953-1966 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  June 1953-April 1966
- Hospital Associations - Fort Worth and Denver Railway, 1960-1969 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  1960-May 1969
- Hospital Associations - Illinois Central Hospital Department, 1957-1971 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Hospital Associations - Illinois Central Hospital Department, 1956-1968 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Hospital Associations - Illinois Central Railroad, 1971-1976 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  September 1971-June 1976
- Hospital Associations - Missouri-Kansas-Texas, 1960-1979 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Hospital Associations - Northern Pacific, 1952-1968 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  1952-November 1968
- Hospital Associations - Santa Fe Coast Lines, 1960-1978 (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Hospital Associations - Santa Fe Gulf Lines, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  January-August 1960
- Hospital Associations - Santa Fe, 1946-1979 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  1946-June 1979
- Hospital Associations - Southern Pacific Texas and Louisiana Lines, 1973-1976 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  November 7, 1973-January 1976
- Hospital Associations - Southern Pacific Company (Texas and Louisiana), 1953-1968 (Box 47, Folder 17)
- Hospital Associations - Spokane, Portland, and Seattle, 1960-1963 (Box 47, Folder 18)
- Hospital Associations - Saint Louis Southwestern Railway, 1960-1973 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  1960-February 1973
- Hospital Association - Texas and Pacific, 1963-1979 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  January 1, 1963-April 1979
- Hospital Associations - Texas and Pacific, 1964-1965 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  1964-May 1965. Mediation Case MB-468: Carrier's arbitrary termination of its agreement with the Texas and Pacific Employees' Hospital Association, dated July 19, 1947, and amendments thereto, involving the treatment of on-duty injuries, change in the phys
- Hospital Associations - Missouri Pacific Employees' Hospital Association, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 22)
- Western Pacific Hospital Associations, 1949-1965 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  1949-May 1965
- Hospital Associations - Gulf Coast Lines, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 24)
- Hospital Associations - Wabash, 1962-1967 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  January 1, 1962-October 1967
- Hospital Associations - CAMAS Prairie Railroad, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Hospital Associations - Fort Terminal Railroad Association, 1968-1971 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Hospital Associations - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1953-1974 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  1953-November 1974
- Hospital Associations - Missouri Pacific, 1964-1966 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  Mediation Case MB-467: Carrier's arbitrary termination of its agreement with the Hospital Association dated March 1, 1961, involving treatment of on-duty injuries and other related matters
- Hospital Associations - Missouri Pacific Gulf District, 1964-1966 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Hospital Associations - Missouri Pacific, 1964-1979 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  January 1, 1964-April 1979
- Hospital Organizations - Harbor Belt Line Railroad, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Hospital Associations - Illinois Central Hospital Department, 1974-1979 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  March 1974-September 10, 1979
- Hospital Associations - Health Maintenance Incorporated of Northern California, 1973-1975 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  November 1973-June 1975
- Hospital Associations - Transportation Hospital Association (Formerly Pacific Electric Hospital), 1946-1962 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Hospital Associations - Southern Pacific (Pacific Lines), 1958-1969 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  January 1, 1958-September 12, 1969
- Hospital Associations - Union Pacific Railroad Employees Hospital Association, 1969-1976 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  1969-April 1976
- Hospital Associations - Union Pacific, 1953-1974 (Box 48, Folder 13)
- A Program of Experiments: 1974 Progress Report, Task Force on Terminals (Box 48, Folder 14)
- Department of Labor - Manpower Training Program, 1971-1973 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  1971-December 31, 1973
- Department of Labor - Manpower Training Program, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 16)
- Department of Labor - Manpower Training Program/Human Resources Development Institute, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  August 1971
- Department of Labor - Manpower Training Program - United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America On-The-Job Training, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 18)
- Manpower Training Program - Jobs, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 19)
- Manpower Training Program - Operation Transition, 1971-1973 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  November 10, 1971-January 1973
- Manpower Training Program - Institutional Training, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 21)
- Manpower Training Program - Work Incentive Program (WIN), 1974 (Box 48, Folder 22)
- Department of Labor - Work Incentive Program, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 23)
- Department of Labor - Work Incentive Program (WIN) - Publicity, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 24)
- Department of Labor - Work Incentive Program (WIN) - Personnel Instructions, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 25)
- Department of Labor - Work Incentive Program (WIN) - Personnel, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 26)
- Department of Labor - Work Incentive Program (WIN) - Training Kits, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  July 1973
- Department of Labor - Work Incentive Program (WIN) - GSA Automobiles, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  May 1973
- Department of Labor - Work Incentive Program (WIN) - Consultants, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 29)
- Department of Labor - Work Incentive Program (WIN) - National Contract (General), 1974 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  November 1974
- Department of Labor - Work Incentive Program (WIN) - Curriculum, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Department of Labor - Financial Correspondence, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Department of Labor - Work Incentive Program (WIN) - Reports, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  March 1973
- Department of Labor - Work Incentive Program (WIN) - Progress Reports, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Department of Labor - Work Incentive Program (WIN) - Job Placement Reports, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Department of Labor - Work Incentive Program (WIN) - Job Support and Follow-up Reports, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Department of Labor - Work Incentive Program (WIN) - Centers, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Department of Labor - Work Incentive Program (WIN) - Teacher Training, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Department of Labor - Work Incentive Program (WIN) - Equipment and Furniture, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Department of Labor - Work Incentive Program (WIN) - In-Service Training of Field Staff, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  October 1973
- Department of Labor - Saint Louis, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Department of Labor - Saint Louis - Financial, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Department of Labor - Work Incentive Program (WIN) - Saint Louis Reports, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Department of Labor - Work Incentive Program (WIN) - Saint Louis Placement, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Department of Labor - Work Incentive Program (WIN) - Saint Louis Job Support and Follow-Up, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Department of Labor - Work Incentive Program (WIN) - Saint Louis Occupational Training Specialists, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Department of Labor - Work Incentive Program (WIN) - San Francisco, 1973-1974 (Box 49, Folder 18)
- Department of Labor - Work Incentive Program (WIN) - San Francisco Financial, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  August 16, 1973
- Department of Labor - Work Incentive Program (WIN) - San Francisco Placement, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  May 14, 1974
- Department of Labor - Work Incentive Program (WIN) - Philadelphia, 1973-1974 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  1973-February 1974
- Office of Emergency Transportation, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  June 1979
- News Items, Information for General Chairmen, 1960-1976 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  January 1, 1960-1976
- United States Governmental Departments, 1960-1979 (Box 49, Folder 24)
- United States Governmental Departments - Commerce, 1949-1977 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  1949-January 1977. Includes Bound Materials
- Department of Commerce - United States Metric Study, 1970-1974 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  June 1970-June 1974. Includes Bound Materials.
- United States Governmental Departments - Treasury, 1964-1979 (Box 49, Folder 27)
- Governmental Departments - Transportation, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  July-November 1978
- Governmental Departments - Transportation, 1977-1978 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  July 1977-June 1978
- Governmental Departments - Transportation, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  July 1978-May 1979
- Governmental Departments - Transportation, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  June-December 1979
- Governmental Departments - Energy Research and Development Administration, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Pensions - Supplemental, 1973-1978 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  January 1973-November 1978
- Piggyback, 1976-1977 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Dual Organizations - Outlaw, 1971-1972 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  July 1, 1971-November 1972
- Political Expenditures - Local Lodges (Board of Trustees), 1974 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Political Expenditures - Local Lodges (Board of Trustees), 1974 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Political Expenditures - Local Lodges (Board of Trustees), 1975 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Political Expenditures - Protests, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Political Expenditures - Protests, 1976-1979 (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Political Expenditures - System Boards (Board of Trustees), 1975 (Box 50, Folder 13)
- Political Expenditures - State Legislative Committees (Board of Trustees), 1975 (Box 50, Folder 14)
- National Transportation Policy, 1973-1978 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  January 1973-1978
- National Transportation Policy - National Defense Transportation Association, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  July 1970. Includes Bound Materials.
- National Safety Council, 1960-1974 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  1960-September 1974. Includes Bound Material.
- Council of Economic Advisors, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Bankrupt Railroads - "Federal" H.R. 7373, 1974-1978 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  April 1, 1974-March 1978
- Bankrupt Railroads - "Federal" H.R. 7373, 1974-1978 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  March 1, 1974-1978
- Reorganization - Railroads, 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  April 1978-1979
- Reorganization - Central Railroad Company of New Jersey, 1971-1975 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- Bankruptcy - Reorganization of Railroads, 1975-1979 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Reorganization - Lehigh Valley Railroad Company, 1971-1974 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- Reorganization - New York, New Haven, and Hartford - Reorganization, Trustees' Loan Guaranty, Trustees' Certificates, 1961-1962 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  1961-December 31, 1962
- Reorganization - New York, New Haven, and Hartford - Reorganization, Trustees' Loan Guaranty, Trustees' Certificates, 1963 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  January 1, 1963
- Reorganization - Penn Central, 1970-1973 (Box 51, Folder 12)
- Reorganization - Reading Railroad Company, 1971-1973 (Box 51, Folder 13)
- Bankruptcy - REA Express, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 14)
- Bankruptcy - REA Express, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  January 19, 1976
- National Railway Labor Conference, 1962-1979 (Box 51, Folder 16)
- Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees (BRAC), 1972 (Box 51, Folder 17)
- Canadian Railway Office of Arbitration, 1973-1979 (Box 51, Folder 18)
- Washington Reading File, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  January 1, 1976-December 22, 1976
- Washington Reading File, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  January 1, 1977-January 15, 1977
- Washington Reading File, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  January 16-December 1977
- Washington Reading File, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  January-June 1978
- Washington Reading File, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  July-September 1978
- Washington Reading File, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  October 1978
- Washington Reading File, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  November 1978
- Washington Reading File, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  December 1978
- Washington Reading File, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  January-April 1979
- Washington Reading File, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 10)
- Washington Reading File, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 11)
- Washington Reading File, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous (Box 53, Folder 1)
- List of Property Names (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Louisville and Nashville Railroad - General (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Louisville and Nashville Railroad, 1966-1969 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Memphis Union Station Company, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Memphis Union Station Co. - General (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Atlanta Terminal Co. - General (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Southern Rail System - General (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Birmingham Terminal - General (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Chattanooga Station Co. - General (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Tennessee, Alabama, and Georgia RY. - General (Box 53, Folder 8)
- Travelers Group Insurance and Employee Benefits (Box 53, Folder 9)
- Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe RY. - General (Box 53, Folder 10)
- Wichita Union Terminal RY. - General (Box 53, Folder 11)
- Toledo, Peoria, and Western RR - General Correspondence (Box 53, Folder 12)
- Tennessee Central RY. Co. - General (Box 53, Folder 13)
- Ort. V. Tennessee Central, Non-Appeal Awards 10395-6-7; NRAB Cases 2048-9-2055 (Box 53, Folder 14)
- TCU v. Tennessee Central - Non-Application Award 13115, CW Tarpley (Box 53, Folder 15)
- Tennessee Central RY. Co. Railway Express (Box 53, Folder 16)
- Galveston, Houston, and Henderson RR - General (Box 53, Folder 17)
- Houston Belt and Terminal RY. Co. - General (Box 53, Folder 18)
- So. Pacific Lines in Texas and LA. - Revision of Agreement (Box 53, Folder 19)
- BRAC-TCU Merger: General Correspondence (Box 53, Folder 20)
- Chicago, North Shore and Milwaukee RY. General (Box 53, Folder 21)
- Western Maryland. - General (Box 53, Folder 22)
- General Chairman Division 86 Correspondence (Box 53, Folder 23)
- District Chairman Division 91 Correspondence (Box 53, Folder 24)
- Bangor and Aroostook RR Co. - General (Box 53, Folder 25)
- Bangor and Aroostook RR Co. - Radio (Box 53, Folder 26)
- Bangor and Aroostook RR Co. (Box 53, Folder 27)
- Great northern Railway - General Correspondence (Box 53, Folder 28)
- King Street Passenger Station (Box 53, Folder 29)
- Toledo Terminal (Box 53, Folder 30)
- Southern Railway (Box 53, Folder 31)
- Miscellaneous Communications (Box 53, Folder 32)
- NC and LN Districts (Box 53, Folder 33)